export const sampleQuestions = [
  { question: "Year Mr. Rewala founded his first startup?", answer: "2016" },
  { question: "What technology Powers crypto currency?", answer: "Blockchain" },
  { question: "Product / service offered by Innovator point?", answer: "Blockchain products" },
  { question: "Which is the best app for crypto exchange for trading?", answer: "Binance" },
  { question: "Theme of The Founder Formula?", answer: "Mindset Mission Momentum" },
  { question: "Tagline or slogan of the Beesolver Technology Pvt Ltd?", answer: "Innovation thinking, always." },
  { question: "On what central idea the whole event was?", answer: "Founders" },
  { question: "Full Form of VPC?", answer: "Value Proposition Canvas" },
  { question: "Who are the podcast hosts?", answer: "Lakshya and Kushagra" },
  { question: "Team Size of E-Cell?", answer: "15" },
  { question: "Under which organization is E-CELL associated with?", answer: "E-Cell IIT Bombay" },
  { question: "What is NEC full form?", answer: "National Entrepreneurship Challenge" },
  { question: "In what collaboration is with E-Cell is?", answer: "IM Punjab" },
  { question: "Names of both founders’ startups?", answer: "Innovator point, Beesolver technology" },
  { question: "First audience question mainly about?", answer: "How to get your first client?" },
  { question: "Tagline of E-Cell?", answer: "Where ideas take life" },
  { question: "What is E-Cell basically for?", answer: "Promoting entrepreneurship and innovation" },
  { question: "What is an incubator?", answer: "Promote early-stage startup" },
  { question: "Name largest Indian unicorn?", answer: "BYJU'S" },
  { question: "In which year E-Cell CGC COE was set up?", answer: "2023" },
  { question: "Which company formerly knowns as grofers?", answer: "Blinkit" },
  { question: "First question asked by president in start of the event?", answer: "What is E-cell?" },
  { question: "From where did Mr. Rewala’s completed his qualifications’?", answer: "Punjab" },
  { question: "What is the tagline given by the Mr. Rewala’s?", answer: "I'm the greatest, I'm the champion" },
  { question: "How many years the beesolver technology has completed?", answer: "11" },
  { question: "What was the learning Mr. Sumit Singh given reference of?", answer: "5 Pandavas" },
  { question: "Which book recommended by Mr. Sumit Singh?", answer: "Good Vibes, Good Life" },
  { question: "When was first website formed?", answer: "1991" },
  { question: "How many commonly used programming languages are there?", answer: "50" },
  { question: "First stage of networking?", answer: "Relationship" },
  { question: "Which Angel Investor did you get to know today?", answer: "Sumit Singh" },
  { question: "Name recent event organized by the E-Cell.", answer: "Eureka" },
  { question: "Indian Shark Tank investor known for Lenskart?", answer: "Peyush Bansal" },
  { question: "Largest Indian conglomerate?", answer: "Tata" },
  { question: "Legal owner of a company?", answer: "Founder" },
  { question: "Stock exchange in Mumbai?", answer: "BSE" },
  { question: "Term for ownership in company?", answer: "Equity" }
];
